NATHAPON TANSIT

Web Developer

24/18 Chomphon Jatuchak Bangkok 10900 090-071-4247 n.tansit@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/nathapontansit

CAREER SUMMARY:

Entry-level junior web developer with a genuine passion for coding and web development. Recently completed a coding bootcamp specializing in front-end technologies, equipped with a background in data engineering and data analytics. Self-motivated and quick learner, ready to take on new challenges and contribute to innovative web development projects.

EDUCATIONS:

2012 - 2016 | Chulalongkorn University

Bachelor of Engineering - Electrical Engineering (2nd Class Honors)

2009 - 2012 | Mahidol Wittayanusorn School

EXPERIENCES:

CJ Express Group Co., Ltd.

Data analyst and Process improvement manager | 2023 - Present

- Develop data management systems for supply chain process improvement.
- Working with the functional team to develop a full data analytics solution.
- Visualize and simplify relevant data for the Supply chain team.
- Update the database with all primary and secondary data sources, clean, and maintain data integrity (Accuracy, Completeness, and Consistency)

MFEC Public Company Limited

Data engineer | 2022 - 2023

- Enterprise Data Warehouse Migration to Cloud Services (Azure)
- Data Integration (Extract, Load, Transform)
- Data Reconciliation (Verify data quality, accuracy and consistency)

Thai AirAsia Co., Ltd.

Student Pilot | 2019 - 2022

- Commercial Pilot License
- Airline Transport Pilot License (Theoretical)

Toyota Motor Thailand Co., Ltd.

Quality Engineer | 2016 - 2018

- Set up and maintain complete vehicle inspection standards
- Analyse and Solve problems occurred in complete vehicle
- · Manage engineering change instructions and other change points
- Supplier audit (Quality issues)

CERTIFICATION:

- Web Development Bootcamp at Skooldio
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900), Data Fundamentals (DP-900)
- Data Analyst Nanodegree by Udacity
- · Road to Data Engineer by DataTH

SKILLS & COMPETENCIES:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TailwindCSS
- React
- Version Control (Git)

- Python
- SQL
- Tableau
- Power BI
- Google Cloud Platform (CloudStorage, BigQuery, Colab)
- Azure Databricks

PROJECT:

E-commerce Website (Group Project)

Link: https://m4-project-sandbox.vercel.app/

- Achieving first place in Sandbox project from web development bootcamp at Skooldio
- Developed a fully functional e-commerce website using ReactJS, TailwindCSS and schdcn/ui
- · Utilized responsive design principles to ensure optimal user experience across various devices
- Utilized Git on GitHub as version control to manage project and collaborate effectively with team members